multi.net.pk 2017-01-08

# Privacy Policy – Multinet Pakistan

We at Multinet take the security and privacy of customer information seriously and we are committed to safeguarding your privacy online. This guide describes how we collect, use and safeguard the information you provide us with when you use our online services.

Personal data is the information you supply that identifies you, for example, your name and address. Anonymous data is information that does not identify you personally, for example, the average length of visit to one of our sites is 10 minutes.

We may gather data about what pages you visit within the service, how long you stayed on a page and the route you took to navigate through the pages. This information helps us monitor the accessibility of our service and what your needs might be. It also helps us to develop and improve our service generally and in direct response to customer requirements.

When you provide your personal details (such as your name, address and contact details) as part of any registration or online form, we collect these personal details. This helps us to build a user profile, from which we can provide a personalised service, unique to you. The greater the information we have from you, the more personalised service we can provide. It will also enable us to contact you, for example, to provide further information in relation to Multinet’s products and services, to get your feedback on your online experiences and/or to find out if you experienced any problems using or completing any registration or online form.

We may also ask you for personal details at other times, for example, if we run a market research questionnaire, competition, or promotion. However, the majority of this data collection is not compulsory.

Multinet is committed to data security. We take measures to ensure that your personal information is held within operating environments that are not available to the public. We take steps to guard against unauthorized access, improper use, alteration, destruction and accidental loss of personal data. This includes rules for all Multinet staff with access to the servers or databases that hold your personal information.
